Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Thank you so much for watching.
Damn it, I don't understand.
But how are you going to kill
what you can't understand?
Paper art.
After image.
My goodness.
You're a wild one, aren't you?
See, prism stone
You backstabbing witch!
I would be a fool to
fight you on even ground.
I know just how strong you are, after all.
I hope you'll forgive me.
What exactly am I seeing right now?
Why are CP-Zero fighting each other?
So, why'd you suddenly turn on these guys?
You have a falling out?
This is Stussy here.
I put both of them to sleep.
What happened to CP-Zero?
Tell us something, man!
Seems she even took Lucci by surprise.
Stussy did it.
That's one less thing to worry about.
Mother of gastric distension!
York, say something, York.
Anything!
I'm done.
I can't eat another bite.
Hey, rise and shine, Back.
We are neck deep in the soup here.
So, who's this Stussy person?
She is a loyal friend who's been working
undercover as a CP0 agent for
over 20 years. Undercover?
That's pretty bold, sending a
spy to an intelligence agency.
It was not part of our original plan,
but that is the way things unfolded.
One issue, Doctor.
I'm afraid my authority
rank is the same as Luchi's.
I can't override his
orders to the Seraphim.
In other words, I can't stop them.
Don't worry, Stacy. You did great.
Lilith and I will take it from here.
Let's get our giant kids back.
We gotta stop those weird
things before it's too late.
At this rate, the whole
crew's gonna get buried.
You're right.
This is quite troubling.
They look hauntingly familiar.
Yeah, no kidding.
Especially... him.
I'm gonna ground them for
a hundred years for this.
Well, at least they made
us a path to the outside.
No, Marcy!
No, Lilith, wait!
Just give them an order
like normal, please!
Okay, freedom.
Hey, Seraphim!
Got an order for you!
guess you're different
after all he's a cold
-blooded killer but he
almost since fear from you.
Out with it.
Who are you?
That really killed me!
Are you okay, Lily?
That's it!
I'm putting an end to this!
Seraphim!
This is in order!
I can't go!
Edison!
Right on time!
You saved me.
Edison!
Oh, no.
Tell me he's okay.
Lilith, darling, don't
fret another moment.
Your thing's safe.
It is so hot!
Holy motility.
Was that a neuropsychiatric
episode or did I see heaven?
I don't know why, but it seems
like they're done fighting.
Hey, you want to tell me
who the hell they are?
Why'd they stop?
Oh, these guys?
They're our sweet little murder
babies, and we're so proud of them.
What she means is they're our cyborgs.
CP0 gave them an order to attack
us, but our authority is higher,
so when we ordered them to stop,
it overrode the previous command.
Oh, what's wrong, Mosshead?
Are you having trouble keeping
up with the rest of the class?
Keep up with this, idiot cook!
Zoro, Mets, deactivate
your dumb ass mouth!
Don't talk to me like a damn cyborg!
Well, we survived that mess,
but what's next on the agenda?
What else? Dr.
Vegapunk gave us an
important mission, remember?
We're getting him off this island safely,
and we're taking all
his satellites with us!
Aw!
Heck yeah, positive vibes!
Wow! Super!
Shaka.
I put Sea Prism Stone
handcuffs on Luchi and Kaku.
Excellent work, Stussy. Thank you.
We're going to have the Straw Hats
take us off the island on their ship.
I think it would be wise
for you to come with us.
Agreed.
Stop inviting people into our
house! Who raised you? Call it.
Hey!
Bonnie!
Mr. Appleman!
Where'd you go?
Wolf!
Hey, Chumper! You find him?
No, it's like they disappeared.
This is weird.
I hope nothing bad happened.
I'll check this way.
Good luck! You too. Thanks!
Man, what a mess.
Hey!
Stop hiding already!
We can't set sail without you!
The Straw Hats encountered Bonnie at sea
and rescued her from a floating alley.
Afterwards, they all traveled
to the future island egghead.
But their plan encountered
an unexpected snag.
Old man!
Dr.
Vegapunk, Stella, disappeared.
This is Sphinx in the New World.
It's the hometown of the
famous pirate Whitebeard.
I was so scared.
I'm so glad you're back, Marco!
I wasn't scared at all, for the record.
The Navy came barging
in here out of nowhere.
I'm sorry, you guys.
That does sound scary!
I wish I'd been here to
protect you from those jerks.
Okay, but I said I wasn't scared.
So tell me, what did they do?
All sorts of stuff.
Those marines were horrible! Huh?
They wanted Whitebeard's treasure!
They were gonna steal it!
Just like a bunch of pirates!
Huh?
What is this?
Drag out the villagers and
gather them all here. Yes, sir!
I won't harm you, as long
as you do what I say.
Which is quite generous of me, since
you're not protected by the law.
And this island's independent
from the world government, right?
I believe Whitebeard's treasure is
hidden somewhere in this country.
Tell me where it is now! Stop this!
We don't know what you're talking about!
This is the first time
I've heard of any treasure!
Oh, well.
That's that, I suppose.
I...
I swear...
You know what I call your defiance!
An act of aggression against
the world government!
So let's do it this way.
I'm going to shoot you one by one.
Will you lead me to the treasure?
Stop it!
The treasure doesn't exist!
Please don't point a gun at my brother!
We may not be able to afford our
taxes, but we still are human beings.
Don't treat us like animals!
You're not scared.
I know Marco isn't here
to protect you right now.
Restrain her!
What are you doing? Let me go!
I want help!
You brutes!
Get your hands off me!
Leave her alone!
She's not a threat!
Don't you hurt her!
Stop it!
Let him go!
Don't mess with my daddy's
hometown, or I'll smash you!
It's Edward Weevil!
We gotta get out of here!
Yeah, let's go! Just leave her!
Why is he here?
I thought we sent troops to arrest him
when they shut down the seven warlords!
Yeah, but those troops were
never heard from again!
No way!
He beat them all!
That's no man!
He's a monster!
Retain to the ship for now!
We'll wait for reinforcements!
This is Vince!
We were attacked by the
former warlord Edward Weevil!
We need backup! Hurry!
And then, the Marines went away!
They just waited out at sea!
We're lucky that big guy
showed up when he did.
Because they were really
going to shoot us?
So he saved the day, huh?
I'm really glad everyone made it out safe.
That's not the end of the story, Marco!
Someone else showed up
and ruined everything.
Navy Admiral Ryokugyu.
My precious weevil resisted so bravely.
But that rat took him away.
Weevil!
Mommy!
You're going to help me
get my son back! My son!
And my treasure!
Edward Newgate's inheritance will be mine!
You hear me?
Mine!
No,
I'm just worried sick
about my sweet boy who
sacrificed his freedom
for his daddy's village!
Oh, Newgate, what have
they done to our baby?
At any rate, I guess I owe him one.
I'm glad he was here for the village.
I know that tone.
You're just like all the others.
You don't believe Weevil is
Whitebeard's real son, do you?
Well, I know someone who can prove it.
Dr.
Vegapunk will show you all.
Admiral, we brought tea cakes for
your meeting as you requested.
Ah, you've tested them
for poison, I assume?
Of course.
I'll take it from here. At ease, kid. Sir!
Pardon the intrusion.
I thought you could use some refreshments?
Allow me to serve you.
I've been meaning to ask you.
Have you ever met Dr.
Vegapunk before?
I have
Just once A long time ago It's hard
to believe that he betrayed you.
Not a bright move for a genius.
Yes, I must say, this is quite
the regrettable turn of events.
It can't be!
Oh, Pacifista!
What's wrong with it?
Hey, stop it!
You're attacking the wrong guys!
We're with the government too!
Hey, did you hear what I said?
Die, you monster!
Wait! Don't shoot!
What the hell did he just do?
It looked like a bubble shield.
They say that's one of
Vegapunk's greatest inventions.
It has the power to repel anything.
Damn it.
It's nothing like the ones in Marineford.
It's a brand new model.
The Pacifista Mark III.
Submit and relocate to Factory B.
Hostile activity confirmed.
We're all gonna die!
Please don't shoot!
We surrender!
You are under arrest.
Please just wait.
Pacifistas never make
decisions on their own.
Who's giving you these orders?
Please don't move.
You'll open your wounds.
And this was supposed to be my day off.
How is the pacifista?
Is it doing its job?
Something bad is happening up there.
Punk, do you copy? It's me.
Punk, say something!
He can't hear me.
The dome is closed.
We're shut out.
I'm sorry, Punk.
I can't protect you.
Go and take care of Punk.
You hear me?
Okay, leave it to me
The Navy hasn't stopped communication,
but they've cut us out of the loop.
Guess that tells us where we stand.
In the world's eyes,
I'm already a traitor.
Might as well do as I please, then.
Pacifista, mark three, activate!
All 50 units, dispatch!
Straw Hat Luffy is going to take Dr.
Vegapunk off the island aboard his ship.
Your mission is to make
sure it departs safely.
Understood.
The Navy is up to something.
Keep an eye on the shore,
something big is about to happen.
Dr.
Vegapunk is your creator, protect him,
no matter what, get him off this island.
Bonnie, please, I'm begging you.
I've heard enough out of you.
Bonnie!
Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
Hey, what happened to you?
It's over.
I tried, but...
I just can't...
Is that you? Dad?
Thought you could run, boy?
Get on your damn feet! Now!
No, please! Go away!
Stop your whining!
You're coming with us! Come here!
No, I'm begging you, let me go,
let me go, someone help me please,
help me!
Stop squirming, move it, come on!
We're not letting you go!
If you escape, they're
gonna execute us all!
But I, I can't, I don't wanna go
back, I don't wanna go back there!
Help me, please go away!
Search your damn boat!
Somebody help!
Help!
Let him go!
Just please me!
Please don't make me go fast!
Stop it!
He said he doesn't want to!
Wait, what's happening?
Why can't I get closer?
Stop your crying, you little shit.
I can't take it anymore.
I'd rather die!
You're strong!
Come here! No!
I'll never go back!
You might as well just kill me!
If I go back, I'll end up dead anyway!
What?
Shut up, kid!
Stop it!
No!
Come on!
Stop it!
You monsters!
I said stop!
It hurts!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
That's enough! Let him go!
I can't watch this anymore!
I can't take it!
Someone help me!
No more!
Please, no more!
Stop hurting him!
Shoot him down!
Bartholomew Kuma is continuing
to climb the Red Line!
He appears to be heading for Paris-Joyal!
Do not let him enter the Holy
Land, no matter the cost!
The Navy's reputation is at stake!
This is our swore duty!
My father's past.
I don't know if I can face it.
I don't know if I have the strength,
but I have to.
I need to find out the truth.
Okay.
I'm ready, Dad.
Kill me again.
I'll stay.
What do you mean you
couldn't find Vegapunk?
There are only so many places he could be!
Maybe there's some secret
passage where you didn't see?
There must be!
No, he's gone.
I ran everywhere looking for the guy.
And now I'm dying and he's still lost.
Oh, come on, really?
Yes, really!
The hover function on his
shoes stopped working.
I think he broke them!
Don't tell people that they're
gonna make me pay for new ones.
Nobody cares about the damn
shoes We're all about to die.
If he's not in the lab, then
where could he have gone?
Just chill out a sec,
Usopp We don't have a sec if we
don't leave now They're gonna
sit a whole fleet of those
suit-wearing sadists after us.
We know but we can't
leave without Vegapunk
What the heck are you trying to pull Mr.
Appleman?
Bonnie's missing too.
Maybe she's calmed down by now.
I know where she is
Huh?
I can see her right here on the monitor.
Wait, you found her?
Never lost her.
Never lost her!
Hey!
What a mess.
Zoro!
I thought we were setting sail.
What are you doing just
sitting around in here?
Well, he kind of had some issues.
Well, I wouldn't blame you for
wanting to tilly-tally a bit.
Just look, it's all so futuristic.
Wow, I'll say!
They even invented a high-tech
hat that shows off your eyebrows!
A fishbowl is your idea
of high-tech, really?
This is quite a wreck.
Shaka, who's Atlas doing? Let me see.
Edison, Lilith, status report.
The statuses?
You still suck!
Move, Lilith.
I just finished the
repairs on Atlas, Shaka.
Come see.
We, plural, we just finished the repairs.
I worked on her just as much as you did.
Hey, gang!
Guess who's back?
She's got dance! Hit me up!
It's human kicks!
Human Atlas! Oh, no!
Matt, look! I'm alive!
Yes, I can see that!
Gosh, she sure is full of energy.
I guess we did a good job.
Hey, girl, hey, looking good. Thanks!
Did you just wake up now?
You kind of missed a lot.
If you want, I'll smack the
drowsies right out of you!
How about you don't and say you didn't?
Oh, good.
I'm glad her face got better.
We had replacement lights ready.
Hey, it's you!
You're the little guy who saved my bacon!
Thanks a bunch, bud!
No problem!
So you've started being
up little girls now, huh?
You creeps are every bit as rotten
as you were when we first met you!
If you so much as look at Robin again,
I'll put you straight in the ground!
Nami, there's nothing
they can do to me now.
That said, I wanted to see Stella,
but it seems something happened.
Unfortunately, we've been faced
with two unpleasant surprises.
First, Stella has disappeared.
Second, we've lost control
of the Frontier Dome.
And what does that mean for us?
It means for the time being we're trapped
inside the level phase with no escape.
If anyone tries to leave laser beams will
incinerate them immediately
are you kidding me?
We're supposed to take
Vegapunk to sea like
urgently aren't we ideally
but we can't do that.
While he's missing what
are we supposed to do
let me handle the dome
you go look for stella.
That's the only solution afforded to us.
Quick question.
You got monitors that show the whole lab,
but you said you can't see Vegapunk on it.
So what's the point in
a search of the place?
Normally, we can see everything,
but not at the moment.
The Seraphim's Rampage did
quite a number on this place.
Many of the Camp Snells are
either lost or unconscious.
We need everyone to check
the unsurveiled areas.
Stella could be incapacitated in
one of the Camp Snell blind spots.
Shaka, this is Pythagoras.
I'm on the third floor of building C.
And it's crickets up here.
I see.
Then check the next building
over while you're there.
We should start looking too.
The sooner we get out of
here, the better after all.
And I might find some future
treasure along the way.
That sounds delightful.
I think I'll come too.
Hey, I don't like the sound of that.
You guys aren't going to
start any trouble, are you?
We would never, right, Amu?
Yeah, let's go with that.
That wasn't convincing at all!
Stay where I can see you.
If you don't mind, I'll search as well.
It's not like him to disappear like this.
Mind if I come along with you?
Of course. I'm grateful.
Susie, let me come too, please.
I'll follow you to the ends of the earth.
All right.
Guess I'd better go too.
Hold up, Mosshead. What's your deal?
I'm looking for some apple guy, right?
Easy.
Not for you.
No way.
Absolutely not.
I'll knock it off.
What the hell's your problem?
If you're out searching, I know
who's going to search for you!
Come on, man. He's right!
Zoro, please don't go!
You too? No, really.
Be a good boy and stay here.
Whatever.
Let's get our search on, my bros!
I won't let Vega pump down!
But he's like a mate out there!
I've got a really bad feeling about this.
Even if we're not Zoro,
we still might get lost.
How did you guys ever
make it out of a port?
Just follow me! Really? Thanks!
York, are you asleep again?
We need help.
You can nap once we're on the ship.
Yeah!
Okay.
Don't know why they wanted me to stick
around so bad, but I guess it's fine.
I'm sure finding one old man
won't be too hard for them.
But damn, you really went all out, huh?
Ugh, I always go all out.
Yeah, fair enough.
Anyway, I never thought I'd
see these assholes again.
Really takes me back.
Remember Water 7?
Ice Pop's place.
I wonder how he's doing.
Now there's a scoop if I ever heard one!
Who would've thunk?
the government power-drunk, and
they're coming for Vegapunk!
Gunning for the greatest
minds in the world again.
Seems Ohadda was a big
enough hit to get a sequel.
But they'll be hard-pressed to spin this!
Vegapunk's a hero all across the seas!
He brought life to towns all around!
His energy tech made him a shining star!
But he's sharing a stage
on Egghead with him!
Fire up the presses!
The World Economic Journal's got a
scorching hot new front page story!
And the headline is,
Emperor of the Sea Straw Hat Luffy wages
war with the Navy on Egghead and holds Dr.
Vegapunk hostage.
No better villain than
a pirate, am I right?
Now, when the government kills Vegapunk,
they won't get any bad publicity.
And they'll be grateful for
my impeccable journalism.
Remind them we take donations.
Yes, sir.
You're not a journalist.
You're just spinning ridiculous lies.
Luffy would never do
such a horrible thing.
You and the government are pathetic.
Phoebe!
Keep your voice down, are you crazy?
The government could be listening
to our every word right now.
What if they got the whole place bugged?
They're gonna squash us
like bugs! Don't dip it!
And don't forget Morgia's
saving our asses.
Get off his tail feathers!
Absolutely not.
I will not be silent about this.
What gives you the right to twist
the truth for your own gain?
Have you no sense of decency?
Those are my clothes
she's wearing, you know?
And I'll never watch them again!
You're so lucky!
Princess Phoebe!
You were crying your eyes
out yesterday, little girl!
And today you're all high and
mighty telling me how to do my job!
I'm a mover and a shaker!
A big news maker!
Who are you?
Newspapers are entertainment!
So I don't care if they're true or not!
Do you know what's going on?
I'll see you soon.
I'll be laughing at you.
I'll be the same song.
If you're a big man!
I won't forget.
I'll be the same song.
I'll be the
same
song.
Thank you.